const qMagooshBank = [
{
    question: "Abtruse",
    answers: ["difficult to understand", "without any attempt at concealment", "completely obvious", "to object or show reluctance"],
    correct: "difficult to understand",
    questionId: "0001",
    description:"Physics textbooks can seem so abtruse to the uninitiated that readers feel as though they are looking at hieroglypics."
},
{
    question: "Abtruse",
    answers: ["without any attempt at concealment", "incomprehensible", "completely obvious", "to object or show reluctance"],
    correct: "incomprehensible",
    questionId: "0002",
    description:"Physics textbooks can seem so abtruse to the uninitiated that readers feel as though they are looking at hieroglypics."
    },
{
    question: "Blatant",
    answers: ["a tirade", "harried", "without any attempt at concealment", "incomprehensible"],
    correct: "without any attempt at concealment",
    questionId: "0003",
    description: "(completely obvious) Allen was often punished in school for blatantly disrespecting teachers."
},
{
    question: "Blatant",
    answers: ["incomprehensible", "a tirade", "gall", "completely obvious"],
    correct: "completely obvious",
    questionId: "0004",
    description: "(without any attempt at concealment) Allen was often punished in school for blatantly disrespecting teachers."
},
{
    question: "Conspicuous",
    answers: ["without any attempt at concealment", "gall", "a tirade", "heretic"],
    correct: "without any attempt at concealment",
    questionId: "0005",
    description: "American basketball player are always "
     +"conspicuous when they go abroad -- not only are they American but some are seven feet tall."
},
{
    question: "Demur",
    answers: ["a tirade", "to object or show reluctance", "gall", "harried"],
    correct: "to object or show reluctance",
    questionId: "0006",
    description: "Wallace dislike the cold, so he demurred when his friends suggested they going to skiing in the Alps."
},
{
    question: "Eclectic",
    answers: ["without any attempt at concealment", "to object or show releuctance", "comprised of a variety of styles", "to object or show reluctance"],
    correct: "comprised of a variety of styles",
    questionId: "0007",
    description: "Joey was known for his eclectic tastes in music, "+
    "one moment dancing to disco the next 'air conducting' along to Bethoven's 9th symphony."
},
{
    question: "Forlon",
    answers: ["the trait of being rude and impertinent", 
    "without any attempt at concealment", 
    "to object or show reluctance", 
    "marked by or showing hopelessness"],
    correct: "marked by or showing hopelessness",
    questionId: "0008",
    description: "After her third dog died, Marcia was simply forlon;"+
    " this time even the possibility of buying a new dog no longer held any joy"
},
{
    question: "Gall",
    answers: ["the trait of being rude and impertinent", 
    "troubled persisitently especially with pretty annoyances", 
    "without any attempt at concealment", 
    "clumsy"],
    correct: "the trait of being rude and impertinent",
    questionId: "0009",
    description: "Even though Carly was only recently hired, "+
    "she had the gall to question her boss's judgement in front of the office"
},
{
    question: "Harried",
    answers: ["dishonorable", 
    "troubled persisitently especially with pretty annoyances", 
    "clumsy", 
    "full of or showing high-spirited merriment"],
    correct: "troubled persisitently especially with pretty annoyances",
    questionId: "0010",
    description: "With a team of new hires to train, Martha was constantly "+
    "harried with little question and could not focus on her projects."
},
{
    question: "Ignoble",
    answers: ["troubled persisitently especially with pretty annoyances", 
    "clumsy", 
    "dishonorable", 
    "full of or showing high-spirited merriment"],
    correct: "dishonorable",
    questionId: "0011",
    description: "In the 1920'th the World series was rigged --an ignoble act which baseball took decades to recover from."
},
{
    question: "Jovial",
    answers: ["dishonorable", 
    "clumsy", 
    "troubled persisitently especially with pretty annoyances", 
    "full of or showing high-spirited merriment"],
    correct: "full of or showing high-spirited merriment",
    questionId: "0012",
    description: "The political candidate and his supporters were jovial once it was clear that she had won"
},
{
    question: "Maladroit",
    answers: [ "clumsy",
    "dishonorable", 
    "troubled persisitently especially with pretty annoyances", 
    "full of or showing high-spirited merriment"],
    correct: "clumsy",
    questionId: "0013",
    description: "As a child she was quite maladroit, but as an adult, she has become an adept dancer"
},
{
    question: "Nonplussed",
    answers: ["dishonorable", 
    "unsure how to act or react", 
    "troubled persisitently especially with pretty annoyances", 
    "full of or showing high-spirited merriment"],
    correct: "unsure how to act or react",
    questionId: "0014",
    description: "Shirely was totally nonplussed when the angry motorist cut her off and then stuck his finger out the window."
},
{
    question: "Ostracize",
    answers: ["dishonorable", 
    "unsure how to act or react", 
    "exclude from a community or group", 
    "full of or showing high-spirited merriment"],
    correct: "exclude from a community or group",
    questionId: "0015",
    description: "Later in his life, Leo tolstoy was ostracized from "+
    "the Russian Orthodox Church for his writtings that contradicted church doctrine."
}
,
{
    question: "Panache",
    answers: ["dishonorable", 
    "unsure how to act or react", 
    "exclude from a community or group", 
    "distinctive and stylish elegance"],
    correct: "distinctive and stylish elegance",
    questionId: "0016",
    description: "Jim, with his typical panache, came to the wedding reception with a top hat, a cane, and a long cape covered in sequins."
}
,
{
    question: "Refractory",
    answers: ["stubbornly resistant to authority or control", 
    "unsure how to act or react", 
    "exclude from a community or group", 
    "distinctive and stylish elegance"],
    correct: "stubbornly resistant to authority or control",
    questionId: "0017",
    description: "Used to studious high school students, Martha was unprepared "+
    "for the refractory Kindergarteners who neither sat still nor listened to a single word she said."
}
,
{
    question: "Sanction",
    answers: ["dishonorable", 
    "A legal penalty for a forbidden action", 
    "exclude from a community or group", 
    "distinctive and stylish elegance"],
    correct: "A legal penalty for a forbidden action",
    questionId: "0018",
    description: "International sanction have been placed on certain shipping lanes that were thought to be involved in human trafficking."
}
,
{
    question: "Tenacious",
    answers: ["dishonorable", 
    "unsure how to act or react", 
    "stubbornly unyielding", 
    "distinctive and stylish elegance"],
    correct: "stubbornly unyielding",
    questionId: "0019",
    description: "Even the most tenacious advocates for gun ownership must admit some of the dangers that firearms present."
}
,
{
    question: "Underscore",
    answers: ["dishonorable", 
    "unsure how to act or react", 
    "exclude from a community or group", 
    "give extra weight to (a communication)"],
    correct: "give extra weight to (a communication)",
    questionId: "0020",
    description: "While the hiking instructor agreed that carrying a first aid kit"+
    " could be a good idea under certain circumstances, he underscored the importance of carrying enough water"
}
,
{
    question: "Venality",
    answers: ["the condition of being susceptible to bribes or corruption", 
    "unsure how to act or react", 
    "describe in detail", 
    "distinctive and stylish elegance"],
    correct: "the condition of being susceptible to bribes or corruption",
    questionId: "0021",
    description: "Even some of the most sacrosanct sporting events are not immune to venality,"+
    " as many of the officials have received substancial bribes to make biased calls"
}
,
{
    question: "Winsome",
    answers: ["dishonorable", 
    "charming in a childlike or naive way", 
    "exclude from a community or group", 
    "describe in detail"],
    correct: "charming in a childlike or naive way",
    questionId: "0022",
    description: "She was winsome by nature, and many people were drawn to this free and playful spirit."
}
,
{
    question: "Admonitory",
    answers: ["dishonorable", 
    "unsure how to act or react", 
    "serving to warn", 
    "distinctive and stylish elegance"],
    correct: "serving to warn",
    questionId: "0023",
    description: "At the assembly, the high school vice-principal gave the students"+
    " an admonitory speech, warning them of the many risks and dangers of prom night."
}
,
{
    question: "Brazen",
    answers: ["describe in detail", 
    "unsure how to act or react", 
    "exclude from a community or group", 
    "unrestained by convention or propriety"],
    correct: "unrestained by convention or propriety",
    questionId: "0024",
    description: "The large donations to the local police department gave the drug cartel the brazen confidence to do their business out in open."
}
,
{
    question: "Contingent",
    answers: ["a gathering of persons representative of some larger group", 
    "unsure how to act or react", 
    "exclude from a community or group", 
    "distinctive and stylish elegance"],
    correct: "a gathering of persons representative of some larger group",
    questionId: "0025",
    description: "A small contingent of those loyal to the king have gathered around the castle to defend it."
}
,
{
    question: "Contingent",
    answers: ["describe in detail", 
    "possible but not certain to occur", 
    "exclude from a community or group", 
    "distinctive and stylish elegance"],
    correct: "possible but not certain to occur",
    questionId: "0026",
    description: "Wheather the former world champions can win again this year is contingent upon none of its star players getting injured."
}
,
{
    question: "Delineate",
    answers: ["possible but not certain to occur", 
    "unsure how to act or react", 
    "describe in detail", 
    "distinctive and stylish elegance"],
    correct: "describe in detail",
    questionId: "0027",
    description: "After a brief summary of proper swimming technique,"+
    " the coach delineated the specifics of each stroke, spending 30 minutes alone on the backstroke."
}
,
{
    question: "Efficacious",
    answers: ["distinctive and stylish elegance", 
    "unsure how to act or react", 
    "exclude from a community or group", 
    "producing the intended result"],
    correct: "producing the intended result",
    questionId: "0028",
    description: "Since Maggie's cough syrup, which had expired five years back, was no longer efficacious, she coughed through the night."
}
,
{
    question: "Fortuitous",
    answers: ["Occuring by happy chance", 
    "unsure how to act or react", 
    "exclude from a community or group", 
    "producing the intended result"],
    correct: "Occuring by happy chance",
    questionId: "0029",
    description: "While the real objects are vastly different sizes in space, the sun and the moon seem to have the same fortuitous size in the sky."
}
,
{
    question: "Garrulous",
    answers: ["dishonorable", 
    "Full of trivial conversation", 
    "Occuring by happy chance", 
    "distinctive and stylish elegance"],
    correct: "Full of trivial conversation",
    questionId: "0030",
    description: "Lynne was garrulous: once, she had a fifteen minute conversation with a stranger before she realized the woman didn't speak english."
}

    ];

export default (n = 5) =>
    Promise.resolve(qMagooshBank.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));
  
